Finding Aid for Alumni Association (University of Michigan) records, 1845-2001
Bentley Historical Library
- Photographs, Circa 1869-1997
  - Michigan Alumnus Magazine files
    - Individuals
      - Wens-Wer (Box 147)
      - Wes-Wey (Box 147)
      - Whe- (Box 147)
      - Whip-Whitk (Box 147)
      - White, A.-White, J (Box 147)
      - White, L.-White, S (Box 147)
      - Whitm-Whitw (Box 147)
      - Wic-Wing (Box 147)
      - Wini-Wir (Box 147)
      - Wink, Helena Knauf (Box 147)
      - Wis-Wit (Box 147)
      - Woh-Wol (Box 147)
      - Wolf, Wolfe, Wolff (Box 147)
      - Won-Woo (Box 147)
      - Wood(s) (Box 147)
      - Wop-Wot (Box 147)
      - Wright (Box 147)
      - Wu-Wy (Box 147)
      - Ya-Ye (Box 147)
      - Yo-Yu (Box 147)
      - Yost, Fielding (Box 147)
      - Young (Box 147)
      - Za- (Box 147)
      - Ze- (Box 147)
      - Zi- (Box 147)
      - Zo-Zy (Box 147)
  - Publicity, undated
    - News and Information Services, undated (Box 169)
    - UNITAS, undated (Box 169)
  - Reunion of Black Graduates, 1987-1992 (with gaps); 2 folders
    - Alumni and Student Exchange, undated (Box 169)
    - Negatives and Proofs, 1987-1991 (with gaps) (Box 169)
    - Notable Alumni, 1990-1992 (Box 169)
    - Reunions, undated (Box 169)
    - Photo Albums, 1976-1996 (with gaps); undated
      - 1st Annual Reunion, 1976; 1 volume (Box 170)
      - 13th Annual Reunion, 1989; 1 oversize volume (Box 170)
      - 20th Annual Reunion, 1996; 3 volumes (Box 170)
      - undated, 1 volume (Box 170)
  - University of Michigan Black Alumni, 1982; undated
    - Leonard F. Sain Awardees, 1982 (Box 169)
      1.) Dr. Donald H. Godbold, PhD-the first African-American Chancellor of an Urban Multi-College Community College District)
      2.) Dr. Alexa Canady, MD-The first American and African American woman to become a neurosurgeon in the United States.
  - Miscellaneous, 1987-1997; undated (Box 169)
- Publications, 1970-2001
  The Publications series (box 169) contains materials from the African American Alumni Council such as affirmative action newspaper clippings, and copies of African American Research Pserspectives. Also included are the Alumni Association's UNITAS newsletter, and Minority Recruitment Program publications; newspaper clippings on racism; the Reunion of Black Graduates Souvenir books; and other publications.
  - African American Alumni Council, 1992-2001; Circa 2013-2014
    - Affirmative Action clippings, 1992-1998; Circa 2013-2014 (Box 169)
    - African American Research Perspectives, 2000-2001 (Box 169)
      Fall 2000; Winter 2001: Special Double Issue
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-2000 (Box 169)
  - Alumni Association, 1989-1995 (with gaps); undated
    - Minority Recruitment Program, 1989-1991 (with gaps); undated (Box 169)
    - UNITAS, 1989-1995 (with gaps)
      - Vol. 1-8, 1989-1995 (with gaps) (Box 169)
  - Racism, 1970-1989 (scattered dates); undated
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1989 (scattered dates); undated (Box 169)
  - Reunion of Black Graduates, 1985-2000
    - Souvenir Books, 1985-2000; 2 folders (Box 169)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993-1996; undated (Box 169)
Bentley Historical Library maintains the University of Michigan Alumni Files Index, 1841-1968, formerly known as the Necrology File or the Necrology File Index.